https://greensfirst.com/privacy-policy-2

Toggle navigation
0 item(s)
Products
PATIENTS / CLIENTS CLICK HERE TO ENTER HEALTHCARE PROVIDER CODE
×
Please enter your healthcare provider code
Submit
Do not have a healthcare provider code?
Click here to continue
* Please make sure that the code is correct or contact your healthcare provider
Greens First Chocolate
Greens First Travel Packet (15 per box)
Greens First Berry Travel Packet (15 per box)
Greens First Chocolate Travel Packets (15 per box)
Greens First Acid Neutralizer PRO
Greens First Acid Neutralizer PRO - Grape (vegan)
: Leading Professionals Recommend and Use The DeAcidify Kit
Kim M.: Wanted to write...
J. Rhodes: " Prior to using Greens First Female my monthly menstrual was terrible,
vomiting, crampin...
Anna Hines: “If you are looking to gain energy or looking to increase your overall wellness, Greens Fir...
Dr. Ken Patterson: A tasting station set up by a wonderful Greens First Healthcare Provider
www.greensfirst.com
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on 11/25/2019
